♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
Hey, Coiny! You're a penny! You're worthless!
Worthless isn't the right word!
You meant to say I'm priceless!
You? Priceless?! Ahahahaha-as IF!
COINY:
Well, at least I have a brain.
AUH!
Whoa, guys. Calm down.
And what would you know, Tennis Ball?
You don't even have ARMS!
Well, at least Tennis Ball knows more than you!
Really, Coiny?
You know, I...I would BARF-
ROCKY:
Bleh!
-if you won Dream Island!
Well, I wouldn't be surprised if I did!
So let's find out who won't win Dream Island.
Last episode, your little team of three lost again.
Go that way to the Cake at Stake place.
♪ Hork hork hork, glorp glorp ♪
♪ Gloop gloop gloop, doot doot ♪
♪ Cake at Stake! ♪
HAHAHAHAHAHA!!!
So the two of you with the most votes will leave the team.
The Grapes will then choose which one of you will
be on their team, and which one will be eliminated.
So that means only one of us is saaafe!
Yes, that's true.
And that safe person happens to be Firey,
who got nine out of the total sixty-one votes.
Tennis Ball and Coiny,
with twenty-two and thirty vote
respectively, you both leave the team.
WHAT?!
Ha-ha!
GRR!
Whoa! Whoa!
If I were you, I would not slap
the most awesome person in the world.
ANNOUNCER:
Coiny and Tennis Ball, you two got the most votes.
It is up to the Squashy Grapes to
decide who will stay or be eliminated.
[SIGH]
Leafy.
Icy.
Blocky.
Please...
let me stay.
Don't think of me as just a Firey slapper.
Think about me as someone
who wants a second chance
at winning Dream Island!
That is the worst speech I've ever-
But if he stays on your team,
he wouldn't do you any good.
He'll just slap Firey all day long.
That's a good point!
Wait, wait, NO!
You don't know how badly I wanna stay!
Well, I think our team will have to pick...
...Tennis Ball.
WHAAAT?!
Coiny, it looks like it's the end for you.
Yay, Tennis Ball! You're on our team!
Actually, this episode,
we're breaking up the teams.
You are the final twelve.
As a result, you're all getting a reward.
BFDI DDSs.
The super fun, portable,
handheld videogame console
will let you play the most
exciting games on twelve screens.
A dodecascreen.
Plus, it's foldable.
So yeah, you can play with those later.
Right now...
you have to climb these ladders.
That is the twelfth contest. Go.
How do I do this?
Come on, people. Let's go!
Ha, ha. Water balloons.
WHOA!
AAAAAAA!
AAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!
YES, number one!
NO, number two!
Oh, no! Oh, nooo!
HEUGH!
- Yeah!
- Yaaay!
Way to go, Pencil.
Good job, Bubble!
Finally!
Oh, now what do we do?
Bleh!
Okay, so now that we are all here,
except for that clumsy Tennis Ball.
let's see the results.
Uh, why are we standing on gray squares?
I'll get to that later.
So anyway, I'm giving you all thirty bonus points.
But this game doesn't even have points!
Well, now it does.
AAAAAAAAAH!!!
Whaaaoooh!
Your score carries over
throughout future episodes.
Oh, great! Boring!
Oh, and from now on, no more Win Tokens.
So what happens to the two
Win Tokens that I already have?
They'll be traded for fifteen points each.
As another bonus, you get points depending
on how well you did in the last contest.
Also, for every vote you got in any of the
previous episodes, that's minus one point.
[LIP SMACKS]
That's weird. Do I taste peanut butter?
Okay, maybe not.
Anyway, Pencil, as you may know,
you're the only person who
still hasn't ever gotten a vote.
Yeah!
Bubble, however, you got one vote.
Oh, no!
WAAUUGH!
Ice Cube got two votes in episodes six and nine.
Wha?
Leafy and Eraser, you each
have gotten three votes.
No!
Match and Pen, you each have gotten four votes.
OMG, seriously?
Well, I'm still in first!
Blocky, you've gotten ten elimination votes.
And Firey, you got a total of fourteen votes.
Hey, Firey!
Rocky's received fifteen votes.
Snowball, you've been voted for
eighteen times, all in episode nine.
Bye-bye.
Ha-ha! Ha-ha!
That laugh isn't fooling anyone!
Tennis Ball, out of everyone here, you've
received the most votes, at twenty-five.
So these are your current scores.
Snowball, Bubble, Rocky, and Tennis Ball,
you are the bottom third, so the voting
will only be between the four of you.
Voters, it is your time to cast your ballots.
The person with the most
votes will be eliminated.
Firey?
Yeah?
I suggest you don't go around setting
people you don't know on fire.
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!